Guide to the Stanford/USE Negotiating Sessions Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford/USE negotiating sessions records
1973-1975
SC0402
Stanford University
2.5 Linear feet (5 boxes)
Minutes from contract negotiations between the University and United Stanford Employees, 1973-1975, and a draft of the agreement, 1974.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
USE, United Stanford Employees, Local 680, S.E.I.U., AFL-CIO, won the right to represent technical, maintenance, and service workers at Stanford University in June of 1973.
Description of the Collection
Minutes from contract negotiations between the University and United Stanford Employees, 1973-1975, and a draft of the agreement, 1974.
Access Terms
Collective bargaining--College employees.; Labor contract.
Collection Contents
- Records
  - Minutes
    - June 22, 1973 - January 14, 1974 (Box 1)
    - January 17, 1974 - April 18, 1974 (Box 2)
    - April 24, 1974 - May 29, 1974 (Box 3)
    - May 30, 1974 - July 30, 1974 (Box 4)
    - May 19, 1975 (Box 4)
  - Draft of agreement (Box 4)
- Additional Materials, Accession ARCH-1992-015
  - Stanford/USE, 1975 May 19 and 1976 Mar 29 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Stanford/USE, 1976 Jul 13 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Stanford/USE, 1976 Jul 29 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Stanford/USE, 1976 Jul 22 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Stanford/USE, 1976 Jul 27 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Stanford/USE, 1976 Jul 29 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Stanford/USE, 1976 Aug 3 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Stanford/USE, 1976 Aug 5 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Stanford/USE, 1976 Aug 12 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Stanford/USE, 1976 Aug 17 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Stanford/USE, 1976 Aug 20 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Stanford/USE, 1976 Sep 3 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Stanford/USE, 1976 Sep 12 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Stanford/USE, 1976 Sep 13 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Stanford/USE, 1976 Sep 14 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Stanford/USE, 1976 Sep 14 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Stanford/USE, 1976 Sep 21 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Stanford/USE, 1976 Sep 23 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Stanford/USE, 1976 Sep 24 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Stanford/USE, 1976 Sep 29 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Stanford/USE, 1976 Oct 1 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Stanford/USE, 1976 Oct 5 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Stanford/USE (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Stanford/USE (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Stanford/USE (Box 1, Folder 25)